onlineseats.com 2013-04-05

# Privacy Policy

## **OnlineSeats.com is an AllianceTickets Website**

**Alliance Tickets** ** & the Onlineseats.com website Commitment to Online Security **Physical, electronic and managerial procedures have been employed to safeguard the security and integrity of personal information. Alliance Tickets encrypts billing information wherever Alliance Tickets requests it. All Alliance Tickets agents and contractors with access to personal information obtained on the Alliance Tickets web sites are also bound to adhere to this policy as part of their contract with Alliance Tickets. To protect the security of information supplied by businesses applying for participation in the BBB _OnLine_ privacy program, businesses are provided user names and passwords to access their information.

**Personal Information that** **Alliance Tickets** **May Collect Online.** Alliance Tickets and the onlineseats.com website collects personal information online, including names, postal and e-mail addresses, phone and facsimile numbers, billing information, vehicle information such as vehicle identification numbers, and complaint information. The Alliance Tickets may also collect business information from sole proprietorships that apply for membership and for program participation, some of which could constitute personal information, as well as personal information from individuals acting solely in their business capacity.

Alliance Tickets does not knowingly collect or maintain any personal information from children under the age of 13. In addition, no part of our sites are designed with the purpose of attracting any person under age 13.

**How Alliance Tickets and Onlineseats.com Uses Personal Information Collected Online**  
Unless you otherwise consent, we will use your personal information only for the purpose for which it is submitted, such as to reply to your emails, handle your complaints, and process billing and business requests related to program participation, and we will use such information to provide operational notices, in program record-keeping and to conduct research on industry marketplace practices. Our research may lead to the publication of aggregate demographical data but will not result in the reporting or publication of any personal information provided to us. At certain points where personal information is collected on our site, there may be a box where you may indicate you would like to be on a mailing list to receive information about other Alliance Tickets programs and services and about ways to support Alliance Tickets. This election box only appears in places where the department collecting personal information maintains such lists. At any time you can add or remove your name from a Alliance Tickets list by contacting us at info@onlinesseats.com.

**How Your Information May Be Shared**  
We never sell or rent your personal information.

Alliance Tickets may also release personal information under the following circumstances:

· Where release is required by law (for example, a subpoena) or regulation or is requested by a government agency;

· Where our records indicate a company may be engaged in fraudulent activity or other deceptive practices that a governmental agency should be made aware of;

· To appropriate persons, where your communication suggests possible harm to others.

**Help Us Keep Your Personal Information Accurate**  
If your personal information changes or you would like to review the personal information we may have on file, please e-mail us with the new information or your review request at [info@onlineseats.com](mailto:info@onlineseats.com). Let us also know what led to your submission of personal information so we may efficiently locate your information.

**Computer Tracking and Cookies**  
Our web sites are not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information not entered by visitors. Our site logs do generate certain kinds of non-identifying site usage data, such as the number of hits and visits to our sites. This information is used for internal purposes by technical support staff to provide better services to the public and may also be provided to others, but again, the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information.

A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Alliance Tickets uses non-identifying cookies to provide easier site navigation and access to forms. You can still use the Alliance Tickets sites if your browser is set to reject cookies. Our cookies do not generate personal data, do not read personal data from your machine and are never tied to anything that could be used to identify you.

**Problems or Complaints with Alliance Tickets Privacy Policy and the onlineseats.com website.** If you have a complaint about Alliance Tickets or the onlineseats.com website compliance with this privacy policy, you may contact us at [info@onlineseats.com](mailto:info@onlineseats.com)
